{
    "id": "37330e7af4fd4717a16ef3b418aa7d91",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Which, Where, And What",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is the house .......................... I was born.",
            "description": "Where can mean 'in which' or 'at which'.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "14790b71104643a29a7006d21fffe8f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the town ....................... I spent my childhood.",
            "description": "Where can mean 'in which'.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "780c462fd9d4484f9322293257afd2c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the town .............................. I spent my childhood.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which. Therefore, the first and the third options are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "in which"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1cf59be1134e47fca1e9ffb2d1ee34a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know a shop ............................ I can find sports shoes?",
            "description": "Where can mean at which",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "at which"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3f0f4f7264fc4daa8d2544448e705ddd"
        },
        {
            "question": "She got married again a few months later, ........................ surprised everybody.",
            "description": "Which can refer to the whole of a previous clause.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5183af55000479a8f9159621179b504"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was impressed by the way ............................. she did it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "in which",
                "what",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af96ce069b84486ca559f83edb6be914"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have got everything ............................ you ordered.",
            "description": "What means 'the things which'. It cannot be used as an ordinary relative pronoun after a noun or pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ea29d8207eb42958aaf16462844399e"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the school ......................... I studied.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "in which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5bfb93730ca94741bcc80815855868e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She may be late ............................ case we ought to wait for her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "in which",
                "in what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33b86f1042eb4270a3d6aeb0e3df8aa3"
        },
        {
            "question": "We moved to the country so that the kids would have a garden .........................",
            "description": "Both options are possible here. The relative pronoun is dropped in an informal style and it is more common to use infinitive + preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "in which to play",
                "to play in",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "77e3cdba845c4bba8d16b2b832d37b85"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the room .............................",
            "description": "The structure with 'that' is common in an informal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "in which I was born",
                "that I was born in",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bf30755c7e844aefbe34920b4dc83e8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The idea ......................... she put forward was interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "020654da9f254df3b5d5abf085090346"
        }
    ]
}